Kris Klingberg

Marketing Sales Executive at AT&T

kris.klingberg@gmail.com

Summary

Sales professional with 10+ years of experience focused on solution selling to small, medium and enterprise businesses. Specialty in designing solutions to integrate mobile technology with existing systems in the healthcare, transportation, construction, and building supply industries. Technical Skills include MS Office and iOS along with:

Languages: JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3 Frameworks/Libraries: jQuery, Bootstrap, Knockout.js (MVVM) Other: Sublime, GitHub, Brackets

Experience

Sales Executive at AT&T

January 2015 - Present (9 months)

Marketing acquisition partner with responsibility to drive growth in employee sponsorship program. • Design marketing material for human resource benefits sites at 500 businesses across all segments • Collaborate with marketing representatives to ensure 10 pieces of ad work is completed on time for publication • Consistently submit material print requests on time while working on 10 projects with different schedules.

IT Solutions Specialist at AT&T

March 2010 - January 2015 (4 years 11 months)

Business development partner with responsibility to drive growth in integrated communication services. • Designed solutions to integrate with existing systems for 1,500 small and medium businesses • Worked in multi-functional team comprised of engineers, application specialists, buyers and suppliers • Consistently built new business relationships that produced over \$250,000 annual revenue

1 recommendation available upon request

Account Executive - Healthcare & Transportation at Verizon Wireless

April 2007 - June 2009 (2 years 3 months)

Mobility solution partner responsible for driving growth in mobile communications of healthcare and transportation industries in Middle and South Georgia. • Designed mobility solutions to integrate with existing systems for healthcare and transportation businesses • Collaborated with solution providers and business partners to ensure final solution met specifications • Consistently built new business relationships to ensure quotas were met or exceeded

Business Account Executive at Verizon Wireless

August 2004 - April 2007 (2 years 9 months)

Business development partner responsible for expansion of wireless data products and services into small and medium sized businesses. • Designed mobility solutions for healthcare and transportation businesses; one led to contract valued at \$1M of revenue • Collaborated with solution providers and business partners to ensure final solution met specifications • Consistently built new business relationships to ensure quotas were met or exceeded

1 recommendation available upon request

Retail Manager at Sprint PCS

September 1999 - August 2004 (5 years)

3 recommendations available upon request

Projects

Frontend Web Developer - Arcade Game Clone

September 2015 to Present

Members:Kris Klingberg

• Clone of the classic game, Frogger. Udacity provided the art assets and game engine. • Coded player, enemies, and other game entities in JavaScript's object-oriented pseudo-classical style. • Created enemy subclasses with different movement patterns and sprites.

oxyGEN Agent of Change Cirruculum

January 2014 to January 2015

Members: Kris Klingberg, Preston Sneed, Gwynn Grandy

• Coordinated areas of responsibility with three other writers • Wrote one of the four sections • Managed deadlines and presented final draft to panel of directors

Skills & Expertise

JavaScript

HTML5

CSS

Strategic Planning

Business Development

Team Leadership

Strategic Partnerships

Sales Operations

Telecommunications

Sales Process

Account Management

Sales

Direct Sales

CRM

B2B

Wireless

Solution Selling

Sales Management

Management

Selling

Unified Communications

Cold Calling

Mobile Devices

Managed Services

Customer Experience

Sales Presentations

Customer Retention

New Business Development

Integration

Salesforce.com

VoIP

Call Centers

Cloud Computing

Product Management

Customer Satisfaction

SaaS

Channel Partners

M2M

Co-location

Enterprise Software

Professional Services

Leadership

Networking

Strategy

Product Marketing

Marketing Strategy

Lead Generation

Retail

Education

Udacity

Nanodgree, Frontend Web Developer, 2014 - 2015

Elgin Community College

Associate of Sciences, Business Management, 1980 - 1985

Activities and Societies: Student Member on the Board of Trustees, Peer Counselor

Languages

English

Kris Klingberg

Marketing Sales Executive at AT&T

kris.klingberg@gmail.com



5 people have recommended Kris

"As a real estate professional serving his housing needs, I found Kris to be; diligent, was clear in defining his needs and prompt follow thru with all documents."

— **Robin Lanese**, was a consultant or contractor to Kris

"Kris and I share a similar client base within the healthcare vertical and he was always attentive and professional when I would pass along referrals to him. I had no hesitation recommending Kris to any of my client base if they were in the need of his products or services."

— Cal Till, Account Manager, Infinity Network Solutions, was with another company when working with Kris at Verizon Wireless

"Kris excels at customer service, business development and personnel management. Honest, hard-working, and dependable. He would be a welcome and valuable addition to any team."

— **Richard Ricks**, *Chief Financial Officer*, *Georgia PCS Management*, managed Kris indirectly at Sprint PCS

"Kris was one of the most exceptional people I have ever had the opportunity to work with. His character is exceptional which in my opinion is an attribute sorely lacking in todays business world. He pays strong attention to detail, is fair and executes the tasks put in front of him. Any organization who employs him will receive a dedicated, energetic hardworking member that will be a long term asset. Good luck Kris! Janis"

— Janis Boatright, was Kris's client

"Ethical, professional, reliable, responsible and loyal. Those are several characteristics that come to mind regarding Kris' tenure with Georgia PCS dba Sprint PCS as a Retail Manager for our stores in the Macon, GA market. In our three districts ranging from Dalton to Macon and Valdosta, he managed one of our larger retail centers."

— **Terry E. Harvin**, *CMO-Director of Sales & Marketing, Georgia PCS dba Sprint PCS*, managed Kris indirectly at Sprint PCS

Contact Kris on LinkedIn